livecloud.com 2011-11-10

# Social Strata Privacy Policy

Social Strata Privacy Policy
Last Updated: November 3, 2011
This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to all products, services, and websites operated by Social Strata, Inc.
(“Social Strata”).
Social Strata is registered with the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Program. This means that
we comply with the Safe Harbor principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity,
Access, and Enforcement.
Information That We Collect
Information That You Provide Us
When you sign up for any account or service operated by Social Strata, we store all information that you
provide to us. This may include personal information like email addresses, your name, passwords, phone
numbers, birth date, gender, and address information. For services that require payment, we also collect
credit card information, which is stored in encrypted form on secure servers, including PCI-compliant
third-party vendors. Once you register and sign in to one of our services, you are not anonymous to us.
In addition, we collect and store information based on the services that you are using. For instance, we may
store the names of communities that you join, the people that you mark as your buddies, content that you
watch, etc.
Browser Cookies
When you use a Social Strata service, we may store certain information in browser cookies. These cookies
identify your browser and allow us to enhance your online experience. Most browsers are configured to
accept cookies, but you may change your browser's settings so that you are informed every time a cookie is
set, or to prevent cookies from being set at all. Please note, however, that many Social Strata services do
not function properly if cookies are disabled.
Advertisers or other third parties do not have access to Social Strata's cookies. However, such advertisers
may set their own cookies. Such cookies are subject to the advertisers' own privacy policies, not this Policy.
Visit Information Via Server Logs
Social Strata records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie
information, and page request.
User Communications
Any email or written correspondence that you send us may be stored.
Transaction Records
Data from any monetary transaction taking place via Social Strata's service may be stored.
Uses of Collected Information
Social Strata uses collected information to enhance your experience online, authenticate you when you sign
in, send notifications, fulfill your requests for services, contact you, customize the advertising or content
that you see, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
Information Sharing

Social Strata does not share personal information with other individuals, organizations, or companies
outside of Social Strata, unless we have your consent or unless:
     • We are working with trusted partners who agree to abide by the rules of this Policy and have
          signed a confidentiality agreement.
     • We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights
          or defend against legal claims.
     • We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action
          regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or potential threats to the physical safety of any
          person.
     • If Social Strata is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets,
          we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a
          different privacy policy.
Note that we may share certain aggregated, non-personal information, such as demographic information,
browser type, and usage statistics. In such cases, the information does not identify you personally.
Profile information collected by sites hosted by Social Strata is collected by the sites themselves. Thus,
you should review the privacy policy for each site before joining sites hosted by Social Strata.
While Social Strata does not provide any personal information to advertisers, it is possible that, if you view
a certain ad, it may have been delivered to you based on targeting demographic criteria (for example, men
who are between 18-24 years of age). Please note that in such situations, the advertiser does not know any
specific personal information about you. You understand, however, that the advertiser will make the
assumption that you meet its particular targeting criteria.
Data Integrity
Social Strata processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected, and in
accordance with the Policy. We review our data collection, storage, and processing practices to ensure that
we only collect, store, and process the personal information needed to provide our services. We depend on
our users to update or correct their own personal information.
Enforcement
Social Strata periodically reviews its compliance with the Policy. If you have questions or concerns, please
contact us at: Social Strata, Inc., ATTN: Social Strata Privacy Administrator, PO Box 1102, Isle of Palms,
SC 29451, USA. If you contact us at this address with your concerns/questions, we will respond. Social
Strata will also cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints regarding
the transfer of personal information that cannot be resolved between Social Strata and you.
Confidentiality and Security
Social Strata restricts access to personal information to Social Strata employees, contractors, and agents
who need to access the information in order to operate, sustain, improve, or repair our services. These
individuals are bound to confidentiality agreements and may be subject to discipline, including termination
and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
We take appropriate security measures to protect your information. These measures include physical,
electronic, and procedural safeguards, as well as software/system security reviews.
Updating Your Personal Information
If you have a hoo.do account, you can edit your account information at any time online. You will need to
sign in to edit your account information. You may also request to have your account deleted entirely. Please

note, however, that requests for account deletion may take up to 30 days to process and archived versions
of your information may remain in our system after deletion.
Changes to This Policy
Social Strata may revise this Policy in the future. We will notify you about significant changes in the way
we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address on your account or through
our help center at http://help.socialstrata.com.
Questions/Comments
If you have any questions or comments regarding Social Strata's Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
Social Strata, Inc.
Social Strata Privacy Administrator
PO Box 1102
Isle of Palms, SC 29451 USA
